Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sides twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob splashing on cam chat
losing their minds michael getting gong alex taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every
night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond
flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yo all facts yo
Gone not tonight Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls we pretend to play
And we're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness, buckle up tight
Boobs flashing on cam chat, losing their minds
Michael getting gong, to Alex taking flight
It's wild, it's wrong, and we do it every night
Paige got him simpin' hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirtin' hard, let the girls react
It's a freak show, party, no filter, all facts
Yeah, all facts
You know the vibe
stream about what you told Elisa about you? Oh, I just said that you were um some little
back stabbing troll that uh unfortunately I did stand up for it one time and tell her
hey you know he's on a bad guy just put him uh you can put him back in the discord if you can
and she did um yeah that was my mistake but uh I didn't tell her anything that was not true
You simply made a joke
You posted on her discord say why don't you tell Lisa that you said you're a better streamer than her blah blah
How is that funny anybody? I don't know. Thank you never say that and never said one terrible thing about her. So
Anyway, but you didn't see I mean
All I said to her was like what I put in the discord so she did kick you out of the discord good
That's all I needed to hear. That's good
Choose a pretty smart. Okay guys, I did
See I missed one of the trip kick videos that I was in or Tom Twip kick actually PWI piece
KICK, and I just watched a little bit and I was like I was like, oh this is funny. You'll see
You'll see what he does pretty funny
That you want to have a look at this one, okay
I do hope you guys enjoy, I think we all will.
So, but I didn't talk to her personally,
but whatever I said about you,
I said it right in front of everybody.
So, I don't know what you're referencing.
You can go ahead and, she thinks you are scary.
I am still in the discord, she thinks I'm scary?
I'm still in the discord too.
She thinks I'm so scary,
don't you think she would kick me out?
I don't know.
She always says I'm sweet in a mild manner person and,
Never had a problem with me at all. I don't know what you're talking about. But anyway
Of course, you're I am banning you. I don't know, you know, I did have a problem with Alex banning people smelly
Just yes, you can join but I'm gonna be watching this video. So you're gonna it's gonna be goes tober
Oh, what are the cats on the island? What's wrong tricks? Come on. Come sit with me
Is he using the owen at Rudy? Come on, let's get Rudy. Hold on.
You're meowing at Rudy?
Oh, Mr. Roode, where are you?
Oh, there you are.
Sitting in the... Hey, Roode.
You're sitting with your back turned at the... Where are you?
Sorry about that. There you go.
Yes, Mr. Roode. Hey, Roode.
hi wanna say hi to this camera oh you're yawning what's wrong tricks do you want attention to
okay come on oh j-dog j-dog like i said um if you can just just block the person i won't put
anything oops oh shit oh fuck i fucked up the camera shit yeah i'm even having a little trouble
But if it's not that important, I will put it on the video and fix it, okay?
Let's have a look, see, okay?
Um, yes.
Well, you can hack, I mean, everyone can have the link, but, um, you will not be coming up, KZ,
because you have not, um, paid your bail.
The ghost come on at my friend.
Hey everybody let's have a look okay here we go guys enjoy and i'll be maybe comment i'll
comment throughout this let's have a look here we go okay here we go ghosty
You're
What's up?
Casey you're not blocked, but oh you're blocked on stream yard, and you will not be unblocked until
On streamer brother. Why are you trying to join?
Sorry to laugh I mean I don't mean to laugh at you, but I mean you picked
You picked the right
Why is that? I don't know. I think this looks like this. Oh, where's the screen? I don't see the shit. Why isn't the
Hold on
By the way, it's like me. Maybe tonight will chill, but I only got a car. I only got so long right now
Okay. Well, do you want to?
I'm gonna stay until I have to go. Okay. Well, I want to yeah, let's you hear me. Okay
Yeah, let me try to fix my camera.
Can you hear me okay?
Yes, let me see if I can fix my camera.
Do you understand the words that are coming out of my mouth?
I do.
Let me fix my camera a little bit.
Okay, here we go.
Fix your personality.
You heard?
I'm just kidding.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, so do you want to watch a little bit of this?
Yeah, let's do it brother. It's your piano. Let's run it. This is funny. This is what I saw so far is this guy's like, oh, I gotta show this. Okay, here we go.
Okay, all good. Yeah, let's run one a little bit. I'm done. Okay, here we go.
My turb, do I love her still hell yeah down the earth if we talking about my heart
Yeah, this shit hurts when I can't feel the damn thing when I'm on the purge
Should not say a damn thing when I'm in a hurry
So I'ma still do my damn thing while I do the worst
My dad told me, hit it, see a hill, anything, said two times, guy can't a shit word
They can't give up, won't keep up by overdose
Oh
Yeah, please I kind of feel and I don't want to be rude here
I kind of feel not disrespect or anything like that, but who made that clip wasn't you this one
And yeah, that we're listening to
You're tripping videos
Listen, I think that's very disrespectful. I think and here. Let me explain why because you know, I like to talk
Let me explain why it's
It was juice world and we all know what happened to juice world. Oh
I don't know it. I don't know
Or she I don't I don't know it's a main
Maybe I'm getting too into it, but like
Little bit meta for
Yeah, I mean, it's pretty fun. I think he does
I'm not crying about AI song because other people that play it passive aggressive about it. I don't give a fuck
It's just like I'm going with the bullshit lies and like the rumors and some of them are like really dark and sick
Like I definitely didn't harm my ex-husband. Um, I'm not part of like any kind of mafia never even like
I'm gonna have like I pay every like my tickets my registration my I'm like every I'm like a very legal person
I've never been arrested for anything like hello
And you literally been here watching it like a fucking bitch so I can do you a favor you can just leave you don't have to watch me
You know it's easy peasy
No, HK. It's not taking the joke seriously. It's a lot of other things that you don't see. It's about antagonizing and like, you know, just bringing up stuff when you're trying to, you know, when you're trying to just let things summer, somebody pokes at you, pokes at you, pokes at you.
What's up?
Hi, once again, I'm gonna turn off my thing. Do you remember when I would be on your show and we had Alexander NYPD?
All these people attacking me calling me names. It would be like a bunch of people coming at me. What did I do?
Defend my own fucking war, right?
Sure
Mm-hmm. I defend my war. I mean, I'm not like having so if people have like issues with like, you know
Certain things that you do and they're like, you know coming at you. What do you think about that?
Like why don't you just like accept it as their that's their opinion. Oh, I do. I do. I mean, it's like what man
But I was gonna do
So that's what I think about it. It happened. You left the panel and then what I think was
that Christine was telling you that it does hurt her. It's a sensitive subject for her as I can
relate. You know, it's like my ex-husband and you know, you thinking that's fucking bullshit,
like I've had something to do with Aaron Carter and all these-
Mm-hmm. Yeah people people people it's what you think so but it's what you allow
He knows all the fucking fucked up shit that J-Dog is done all this fucking shit
But you know other people
He'll not that person on purpose just to talk about me all day long
You know I have no respect for people that will bend over for doxers for disgusting like J-Dog
There are criminals and you know see this is that you nodding your hair blah blah blah blah
you want to do this you can go ahead and do it you know i mean you're literally like digging
yourself even more you're not here to communicate you're not here to listen go make you actually
here for attention you will never take responsibility and that's the way it goes i don't
want a fake friendship i don't want a fake friendship so basically a french writer like you
Listen, I'm not a fucking fence rider. I'm just literally doing my life. People are coming here and they're going
I'm not inviting anybody like you come here or whatever this
You already came here like 70 times and you left like what the fuck am I fucking fence writings?
Look, I'm not in the mood like you're like, you know what it is. Maybe you're like
And you know what you don't have to you can leave
You came up here, you went out like the first guest, the second guest, the third guest, now you're bored and you're just whining.
I haven't gone after anybody really. I was all trying to tell jokes with people.
I don't ever spazz on the commas first. He's been spazzing out all night. This guy has pulled out his dick on my stream three times
Be very careful
He doesn't farm on but he does he is
Just wait for it
You crashed out hard on the commas first selling face you're gonna get clipped
I'm gonna get a club for being called.
Good times outreach.
I probably duo you with some apologies,
Bita, for like, you know, for everything, you know,
for not like...
Sticking up for you, like, you know, like maybe not for being the best friend and
You don't have to be a best friend and you don't have to stick up for me
You just got to you know not entertain the bullshit when it's sensitive things like when it comes down to you know
People like, you know, like just take me or Christine for example. We told you several times, you know, you're talking about
People that are not either here or for her. This is like, you know, she's kind of an activist even if she does she's a nurse
So it's like she's a supporter of yours. We are, you know, women
It's like kind of sensitive like why go and make a title about it. You know, that's it
Because she was saying oh, well, I wasn't I wasn't doing what you're saying. I was doing and I was like, yeah, you were on
to share with Crystal and you were laughing at what she was saying because nobody takes
Crystal really seriously when she goes off on people because she makes sense about everybody.
Literally, she says, I'm a bad person, I'm evil. I'm just like, I'm, they won't want me.
No, but, but some of the stuff that Crystal was saying wasn't even, it was like, she was talking
about her offing children, you know? That sounds funny.
It was bad, but it was like so ridiculous.
But it is like there's a line where it's not funny where you're like listen that's I'm not gonna
I'm gonna put you backstage. You're not gonna be talking about somebody like that. That's disgusting
You're not gonna entertain it and egg it on and be like and what else and tell me more and then
Okay, once you make a mistake like that and you are told several times by her and summer
and other people this bothers me, you just double down, triple down, like, I don't know,
you keep doing it over and over. Sorry, the times you keep interrupting. So I have to
play, you know.
Frickin' put you backstage, all right?
When you see somebody like a J-dog
making up rumors and gossip about me
and somebody like Alexander Mayer that goes on
and does like conspires to everything,
you mod everybody over there and you let it go on
and not, hold on, I'm talking now.
You let it go on and on and you're like,
it's not a big deal, it's a joke.
You know, you're actually hurting people
by just like co-signing with it?
And I regret that.
So you're siding with me.
I thought you were trying to come against me.
Well, you interrupt so much that good times
you like to hear yourself just talk.
I believe people should be free to do whatever you want.
All right, we got it, we got it.
We know, we got it.
Longest to not hurting other people, right?
Yeah, exactly.
And as long as that you're not like spreading false narratives
about other people and laughing and joking about it,
you know, because some things that it could be, you know,
it could you know it's almost antagonizing it's like like poking you know and then you're poking at
people's emotions and it sucks it's not really cool you all make a lot of judgments and sometimes
we're here I don't know would you let psyche speak god you love good time do it again in truck
I react based on being myself being triggers and I have triggers right and
it's like a community know how to push buttons and stuff and so a lot of times
I'm just reacting instead of like acting right and so it's like I do have to
have a lot of stuff to work on myself and it's like people like you like help
you know bring awareness to myself and so ultimately no matter how
Mad or anybody isn't me. It's like it does help. It's helped me to understand things. You know, not the most
socially advanced person, right? And so back up, you know, and the Christine thing I do regret
Because she never did anything wrong to me. Like I mean, so I wasn't it wasn't like oh
I'm gonna go try to slander Christine. I'm gonna do this or that right? It's like I was just like
caught up in the moment and I was like, oh, this is kind of
She's saying ridiculous things, you know, she's, oh, she's on her medicine again or something or offer medicine. Well, I don't know, whatever.
What, now? Like, listen, then you did it again, and then you went and like made a title about it.
Yeah, we were talking yesterday about, like, I was like, well, Christine, you were on with Crystal and Crystal was saying this up and you were just laughing about it.
Crystal, Christine wasn't in that conversation. Maybe when they were laughing, it wasn't that weird of a subject that what Crystal was talking about. It was a whole different way of a different level. Okay.
So, I mean, it wasn't about her saying, Crystal, you, you know, Christine, you, you know, her children, which is very, like she actually helps children. So she wasn't there to defend herself.
could have just been like, hey, let's not talk about Christine move on.
Let her talk about blah, blah, blah, something else, Crystal.
But then let's forget that.
That was a mistake that happened.
But then you clipped it and then you did it again.
And then you folks have it again and then again.
But I was saying to hold on to Christine.
Yeah, I was like I was saying the whole time to Crystal. I was like Christine if you're here get up here right now
I was like I want to hear that was like no that doesn't sound like Christine that I know I know
I was saying like people were saying I agree with her. I didn't agree with her one time
You can watch the clip. I was saying no no no crystal. I was like no, but I was a bit sometimes I was acting like
You're talking about Christina. We know like I was like I thought I was being
Sarcastic or like a little bit like you know the cecius or whatever, but
Maybe it seemed like I was agreeing with her or endorsing her.
I do not anyway.
Christine is a wonderful, wonderful, I respect nurses so much and so I have affection for
nurses and I have a lot of nurses and medical people on my show.
You have people on your chat that say that I asked my husband, both of my exes, I don't
know, somebody named Jar Jar, I have things that are done with my animals, you know.
I've never mentioned you and your cats, I know you love them.
No, you just like, you just love to come on live and act like, well,
Bita's mad at me.
Bita said this and that because I got messages from you saying, Bita, you know what?
I'm sorry, you know, I'm going to just lay off.
You do your thing.
I said, you too.
love you, love you too. And what do you do? Go back again and play. Listen, let me tell you
something. Maybe the woman that you dealt with in your life before, they might have had dry biscuit,
but my shit is fucking juicy. There's a reason why there's a, you know, there's a virgin fucking
So stop telling people since I turn 50. You don't know what happened like a few months in my life.
I did have somebody very close to me pass away. No, I did not have anything to do with that.
If you are a real friend and checked in once in a while and called and talked to like as a human
being instead of going there and coming up with your own assumptions, the person that doesn't like
I don't know, there's a lot of mutual people that don't like either one of them.
Her name is Kate, right?
I don't think this has anything to do with Kate at all.
Let me finish. I was going to say, Kate, replayed.
your show, like, or I came on and everything.
And even Kate, he was like,
she's like, oh, look at, look at,
we're gonna see fucking Psyche embarrass himself.
She was like, wow, she's like,
I had Bita like yelling at me like that
and then Bronzeberg yelling at me.
She's like, I would have been a bitch too.
You know, it's like, I got empathy from her,
you know, because she's like, wow.
Really I watched that back it was no I didn't I was not close enough to my microphone
I don't think and I was kind of quiet
Did you have empathy when Alexander McQueen and all these people are yelling at me
J-Dog is accusing me of stuff like that or when you have Alex and Alexander
Me are sitting up there bringing up my personal relationships my family
did you think that for a second other people that you've done the same thing to on the panel don't
have a right to be upset and go at you or what you said about bronze bird you sit there and you
make fun of him you're like telling him oh you're below me because you have less subscribers
or blah blah blah blah or like you know what was he saying to me be that what was he saying to me
I'm right here, if you guys sign in and say to me, we could talk about it bro.
I will, you're a fucking bronze chicken.
See?
Okay that's corny, but if you guys sign in and say to me, you could talk to me.
I will, I don't have anything to say to you bronze chicken.
You can have a conversation. You're being naughty already. You're being naughty. He hasn't said nothing. He just came up here and he said, can we have a conversation?
Let's discuss this. Let's discuss this because you're not real. You're fake and you know that. I don't understand why you can't be real and you can't tell Bita why you was making A.I. diss songs towards her.
Being playful. No, you was not being playful. You was in your feelings and you was making AI diss songs towards beta
Because beta was exposing the real you and you didn't like
Just like every single time you come on a panel
You want to shut the fuck up while I'm talking or you still want to run your mouth? Oh, wow
You were talking over me the entire time
Dirty ass motherfucker
Like bro, I told you right no fucking chat asshole. So like I said, why would you make an AI diss songs towards beta?
Why why would you get in all upset when you got kicked off of summer's panel?
To speak for me he joined right now and he has his issues with psyche and you know
Maybe they can resolve it.
No, it's not, it's not a result of anything.
Trust me, uh, Kamanka, I have my heart in school.
I have a lot of things.
I'm like, trust me.
Trust me.
I have a lot.
I'm on camera, Bronzebird.
Your boy, what is this?
You can talk about me not being on camera.
It doesn't make a difference.
I'm not on camera either.
And neither is hot enough.
You don't give a shit.
You don't give a shit about your community.
You only give a shit about your channel.
That's what you give a fuck about.
You backstab your friends,
and then everybody calls you out about it,
Make a stream about it then you talk shit about my channel as a way to sit up there and scapegoat to sit up there
I have something to say about me. I don't think we'll fuck you ever come to my streams
You know why there's only real people coming to my streams not fake motherfuckers like you that sit up there
I'm gonna talk about your channel all day on takeout
Irrelevant you're a little alright you guys can you like listen listen, I try to be cordial with the scumbag
But no, I used to come to your channel you guys to be fuck psyche yo
I can't stand fake motherfuckers like Psyche, yo.
Okay, Psyche, why are you, when he doesn't want it,
when he doesn't, he has his opinion.
Why is that upset you so much?
You always know how Bronze Bird was.
He's going to be stern about his beliefs and what he thinks.
They didn't like me, so he's going to like, you know,
say, oh, you dumb motherfuckin' griffin'
mother son of a bitch.
You are a grifter.
You proved it yourself.
You shit it on your friends when it came to your streams.
When people try to support you dumbass, you sat there and went over to Emma and fucking Jordana, bro
You were like too much. I don't give a fuck, bro. That's what you did. Every single time it came to your channel
You shit it on your own friends. That's why I call you fake. You dumb fuck
Psyche, you're fake. You don't have a community you go to. You shit on your friends and every time you want to come on your stream
It's about oh, I went on tiktok and I got 70,000 views and blah blah blah. I have more views than you, Romsberg
Like I said, why do you think you're better than me because you have a thousand more subs than me?
Why do you think you're better than me?
I'm just gonna interrupt you.
Oh, bro, I'm sorry!
Answer the question.
What's the question?
Why do you think you're better than me because you have one thousand more subs than me?
I don't think I'm better than you.
You say it all the time. You wanna make fun of my fucking channel and shit.
I'm not gonna give up on your chan- are you taking so personally cuz you be- you like-
I don't take it personally, but you love to make it a reference.
You know how Psyche likes to run away from his problems?
He doesn't like to confront a real man.
That's why he likes to go for little jugglers and dumb shit.
And I'm right here.
Okay, go ahead.
What's your point?
Because you was talking shit about my channel.
You was talking shit about my channel,
but you needed people to make your channel hot.
That's the problem- that's the thing you don't understand.
that's why i'm better than you and i'm more real than you ever be in your life
i'm better than you you're real and you mad you're real mr bro brooklyn streets i'm broke what
let's not talk about money bro you can really get into that conversation because you ask me for
money you ask me for money psyche don't start talking shit about nothing don't do that because
you sitting in your house being dirty as fuck bro don't do that don't do that
with your dirty ass nails and your dirty ass couch.
Don't do that.
You don't want to talk about broke, bro.
I will drag the fuck out of you about your cleanness.
I'm afraid of you, Bronzeberg.
You mad dirty.
You sit up there and cry about how your nails is dirty on strings
as everybody talks about how dirty you are.
You're dirty.
You're not clean.
You don't shower.
You sit on your cat's shit, this fucking couch and shit.
the fuck out of here don't you ever talk about my finances right now psyche and then don't get mad
when he's giving it back to you you just said he's broken he fucking you don't know you won't
know shit about that financial situation you ask me for money remember that's what i said i thought
i said bronc and i said something about brooklyn right right and she's like i'm calling him and
then that turned into the narrative did i ever say that no
I just thought to him in New York, right?
So there we go.
Remember that, Psyche?
Oh, okay.
The fuck out of here?
You were sitting up there stripping for fucking trolls to get your channel back for $9.
Let's talk about that shit.
I never had to do that shit.
Even if I cammed up, I still would be that dude that's really doing you.
Let's talk about that shit. You fucking cloud chaser. Everybody know you a fucking cloud chaser psyche
That's why I call you fake. You shit on your friends. You shit it on beta
You shit it on Tracy. You shit it on Christine. You shit it on flirty diamond. You shit it on every single person
That can't be a fucking panel. You fake fuck
Fuck you
Want to sit up there and talk about my financial situation bitch? I wish you would
really
Everybody's entitled to their opinion including you Samantha Avery, but you're not noticing how psyche is sitting there
I don't know taking your responsibility putting down another man. Let's don't forget some of the racist shit
That we're not gonna go back and talk about that he allowed like you know me
Like he allowed you to sit up there and talk out on me.
You don't know.
Just get in the car and go back and force them out for every.
I mean, I've given you enough respect to just tell you
you have your own opinion too.
Things don't go well on my panel.
Psyche takes it out on me, not other people.
He takes it out on me.
Don't be passive aggressive.
Bumper does like making good points.
And like, you know, you're just like fishing in.
You're like, oh, you're just your dad,
and you don't want him to get upset.
You're calling him poor, but I don't see Brunsberg fucking saying he needs money to host a panel or like
Thank you. I'm not asking people for ten dollars to join a panel. You are, psyche.
What are you talking about?
You know what, you know how low my last stream was? I had only five viewers in my stream and still had my shit down for four hours.
So you want to talk shit? Talk shit, bro. You know what, I'll never be, I'll never be a money-hungry motherfucker like you
that sit up there telling people to come up on the stream for ten dollars. That's what you do.
Wow, and I make the ten dollars, don't I?
You call a bitch? Yeah.
So, what are you gonna complain about?
Because you need it, you desperate bitch.
If you don't wanna be on these panels, get the fuck off of YouTube
and go to TikTok.
You get your 70,000 viewers.
You wanna get monetized so bad.
Big mother fucker.
You wanna sit out there and go to IP2
and you can handle motherfuckers that was on your panel.
Let him speak.
Fuck psyche.
You fake fuck.
Don't you ever talk about my finalist situation?
I think it's not a competition, Psyche.
That's where you are always thinking competitively.
You mess with me.
You're like, yeah, you have this many people watching you,
or this, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm like, I told you, Psyche, it doesn't matter.
None of that fucking shit matter.
There's like times where I'm off
and you're gonna get a lot of fucking viewers.
It just depends on who's live, who's on the panel.
It's just a lot of different things, okay?
Uh, okay. Uh, Rando. Yeah, if, uh, if you consider winning, just being screamed over.
I had my, guys, could you even hear me? I had like a very, very low mic, right?
Is that, that's just winning? Just having a, just like, uh, you know, angry person screaming.
I mean, that's just winning. I can just go...
You know put my mic all the way up and have like three people just yelling shit and what they're true or not, right?
Thank you. I wouldn't yes. Yes, Mason. Hold on one second. So that's the clip. Hold on. So that's the clip
But uh, yeah, thank you. Thank you. Get a life. Yes
What's up Mason? Hey, hey, so you check out that video. I'll set you to your Gmail
It's a video of me like that I played at the drums at the guitar center just the other day
I went back there to play the drums like again. It's like yeah, I want you to see it
Tell me what you think about it once you watch it psych. Okay. Let me see Mason. Where's my friend Mason?
So I sent you a new like a video. It's like me on the drugs like playing at the guitar center. Good my
Okay, so
Let's see you're playing like don't me to show it to the chat or
You can show it. Yeah, you show it like you did like other videos you're showing before
So so that's the way people know it's like that way people know that I still play the drums
You know like and they don't think I just don't play the drums when I really do and stuff like that
We know you play the drums. I thought I did I'm just trying to prove. Yeah, I'm just trying to prove a point though
Yeah, I know sometimes it's like, you know if you try to prove stuff sometimes it like
Doesn't almost really help because we know your drum. I know your drummer and it's like whoever doesn't yeah, but psyche
Yeah, but psyche there's people that would say stuff. That's not even like right. I mean like true
They would say like saying stuff to you and it's like sometimes if you just try to defend yourself
It just makes things worse and it's like so yeah, it's like just just be confident in yourself
I mean the people that know you will
Well, I have your back, you know, but don't you don't don't have to worry about yeah
Because they're gonna try to say oh no matter what you say, they're gonna try to say whatever you know just to
Try to like you believe that I do though, right?
You know, of course I do I know though I know the story about you know
Yeah, I hope you play I hope you get some drums again, too
I want you to get your drums, you know a drum set back so I keep but I but the other days like you like yesterday
I want to the guitar center again to go back to try out drums and they have new drum set out this time
They don't have the ones that that used to be there. They set up a new drum set in there. Oh cool
Hey, so did you see the clip Mason? What do you think of that clip? Huh? What do you think of that clip? We just watched
Yeah, it was a lot of like a drama. I think it's called like, you know, there was some drama, right?
Do you think I think I was demolished in that clip or do you think that I did a good job?
What do you think?
Psycho, it's like they were trying to come at you though, right?
Like whoever was that guy that was talking to you in it, right? Yeah, that guy, right? Wasn't he rude?
Same yeah, the one that the last the last guy that was talked to you in the video psyche. Yeah, I saw I saw
Um, let's see something to my password. Okay. One second. Okay. So how have you been Mason?
I did talk to Natalie Mason because you asked me like, you know, what happened with on on Facebook?
You know what happened? I never got back to her. No, it's like, I never got back to her ever since you
I found out what happened, you know, you know what happened
What happened?
Because you asked why did she on another or why did she block you on facebook? Right? Yeah. Do you know?
Do you have any idea why?
No, like tell me why though. It's like do you remember you're trying to like call her you remember that?
Yeah
How many times did you try to call her?
Different times, but how many times it's like did you like that that one time how many times did you dial her I?
Did it different times?
How many like, you know, huh eight times eight times nine times ten times
like four or five times I think.
Okay, when somebody pushes like ignore and stuff,
yeah, maybe it's like wait, maybe it's gonna be a big thing.
Maybe it means they're busy
and then it's like sometimes people might get
a little overwhelmed, you know?
And so that might've been what happened, okay?
I don't think, I mean, she doesn't hate you or anything
but it's just like, you know,
probably better just to talk to her on panels and stuff.
Okay, I got the mollusk rando. What do you think? Yo, I wanted to hear Mason play the drums
Why are you like this missing him? I wanted to hear
Can you pull it up on like you're not doing a justice over
You play look he's really good
You're okay
No, it's not that good of a clip, but I mean yeah looks like you play right you can see him play
Yeah, she's holding the beat. I think yeah, I want to hear it though
Like that loud you can't pull it up on the fucking
I'm sure if it was one of your AI clips should be up like instantaneously
You dirty motherfuckers come on bro seriously, I'm just kidding chill bro chill chill
All right, we could very good Mason. I'm impressed. I'm actually very impressed and that's a good clip. Yeah, good job
Thank you. What's like you sounded good? It's like you thought it was me because
Like you noticed it was me because you saw you saw you saw the me in the video, right? Yeah, we know what you do
Oh, thank you. You got his coffee McDonald's coffee house like he
Left and I poured a bunch of Irish cream in it was really good
Oh, that's what's up. Hell. Yeah. So how you doing today? So I can be doing good, bro. Yeah
Yeah, my neighbors give that as a wedding
Yeah
Take a joke. That was really it was just really hilarious casey. It was a really hilarious
You hear one person lap on the panel. No, he laughed dude. I was explaining to him
He can't understand like why he's not allowed man after he did what he did. It's like that's really unforgivable shit right there
I don't think that you know you're like slow but you're acting slow you're acting slow
everyday you come here and I say okay you want to come on the panel you can pay a little fine
right and uh then you're like I don't understand you're like can I come on the panel and like
negotiate no you can't you can sit in the chat and negotiate are you blocked right now very easily
Yeah
You I mean it's like J. No, that was me J. No, that was me that he was showing on the video on the drum
Yeah, I saw that man. That was badass. That's really cool. I saw you you played the drums really nice man
He can hold a beat dude
I just went back to the guitar center just the other day like yesterday
My I wanted to go play the drums and they had a new drum set that's set up there and I got on it
I started playing on it
Hell yeah, that's cool, man
Mason give me a sec psyche so okay, what made you think it was a good idea to play that clip if you getting totally destroyed
Like I didn't know that happened if I didn't watch that episode a few days ago
What does it mean? I was totally destroyed. So what do you mean? I fucking totally destroyed your own panel?
Why would you replay that?
I don't because I don't feel like I was totally destroyed. I don't believe I don't believe that at all. Okay. All right, come on
So if you're a bully you win, right? If you're just like forget about it pretend like it never happened
Go go to the guitar center get a better mic talk over Bronsburg
You're better now rando. Do you have a digital audio interface?
I don't know you idiot. Go to guitar center. Talk to Mason, dude. So I keep you to step your audio game up
You mother fucker. I used I used to like yeah
Like I used to have a drum set. So I want to guitar six. I don't have
Mason maybe like a little like I'm like a water jug or something start putting quarters in it and save up for a drum set, right?
I want you to get drums because you're so talented, you should like have them to play any time you want, you know
I know how to play the drums pretty good. So I just haven't done it without a drum set for a while now
Well, I was impressed and so good job, okay?
So I got back to doing it. I got back to doing it again just the other day yesterday
Good, I'm proud of you. Good job
What's that noise?
Hello? Somebody like
What's going why's ghost posted up all quiet and shit? What's he doing? What's goes through?
Go's are you here?
You're
Microphone on I don't yeah, his microphones off. I mean he might be at work. I gotta jump dude. Hey, thanks for letting me on site
Dust yourself off, you know
I am fucking do a round two with this with this bronze card
You're the only reason like they said they try to say like bronze bird is cuz he out of the mic how allowed
I mean if I was like, you know, you hear me because then they were saying oh you're talking about his financial situation
When it's very clear in that clip I said something about Brooklyn or something like that instead of like yeah
Now that's a narrative like I'm making fun of his finance. I don't know anything about his finances
It could be a billionaire for all I know I have no idea
Hey, yeah, I said hey well it's like because he has like he had like two like three hour lives
about me in a row I was like well I would do maybe a lot about him but I don't even know
one thing about him nor do I really care but if anyone has an interesting story
or something you know let me know that's I'd say give me his name and address so I can give
it I never have docs anybody and so I think Empress Janet knows who he is she has some
I remember when he used to simp on Janet. I'm sorry. Yeah, I remember on beat us. He would always simp on her all the time
And I was like, I remember when there's clips we could go back on rumble. There's clips
I mean, I can go back into my archive. I have to find the clips, but yeah, he was sipping on her hardcore. And that's like, oh hell, yeah
But um, yeah, anyway
You know, who cares?
What's that noise who's making kissing noises Mason, is that you?
Kissing noises. I hear
You're that no, no, no psyche. That's not me. What was that? It's not ghost or J-Dogg or me
No, J-Dogg. What's that? No, what are those noises in the back? Are those noises? No, no, no, no, look it
I hear like I'm gonna turn my camera on
See I'm on sign. Okay Mason. Okay. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe it's just
Maybe the background
Maybe maybe there's no he's just back here. I'll go somewhere. There's more
It's kind of weird. Okay. Well, it's like I'm trying to tell you wasn't I didn't do anything
It's like it wasn't me. I know but if you think yeah, I'm a funny. No, I know I know it's not
but if you think like
I was destroyed, even Kate was watching.
She's like, well, they're all talking over him
and the mic's really low and you can't hear.
I mean, right?
And she's not going to be like, go out of her way.
She actually did say some really pretty kind things.
And so I'm happy that, you know,
I, you know, I, you know, I go to her show and I'm able to talk to her and stuff.
And she's a, you know, I never had a problem with Kate, um, you know, other than there
was like, you know, a little bit of trollish stuff going back and forth to this when we
first met.
But, you know, she's a, I would say, I think I got, I think you guys got past that already,
huh?
Yeah.
Yeah
I know so many things like oh, well she did this to me and this to me. It's like
It's like I really try to judge people based on like my own relationship
Like just number 101 and it's like, you know, I don't like to go messing with my friends
But it's like it's still I want people to be able to fight their own battles, especially in this
panel verse and it's like, you know
It's always nice to have somebody a friend stick up for you when you're not there
Um, but, you know, um, people, you know, I can't be blamed.
I'm constantly getting blamed for what other people said, or if I didn't like kick them
off.
They said this or that.
It's like, you know, how about just defend, like they said, because they're never like
really mad at the other person.
It's always like, but they remain mad at me, right?
And I didn't even say anything.
Right.
So.
Anyway
It's always gonna be they're always gonna try to blame you for something man
Hey, but next time you want to go up against the Bronx bird man
If you need somebody else like there man, let me know man. I'll back you up. I'll be there back you up
If I'm not there, then it's like I mean if you
Well, even if I'm in the chat, even if I'm in the chat, like when I'm in the chat, too, they just fucking cut, they time me out.
That's why I get, that's the reason why I jump on panels, because I fucking timed out.
And Vita didn't do it. She didn't even know who it was. Like, again, like she didn't quite figure out who was doing it.
Um, yeah, I'll type something in the chat and then all of a sudden I'm like timed out and so and then they're like saying
Oh, you're a coward love love. Do I go a battle and if I leave it's not because I'm like running
it's because I can't get a point out or speak and
Here I have a place where I can speak and so
Is anyone gonna fault me for that? Yeah, you seem to but
Hey guys, how's the chat doing and whatever I want to talk to address KZ whatever he said
He was trying to bait me into letting him up by saying oh, I talked to Elisa about you
And I can't believe what you said about I didn't talk to her personally about you
I wouldn't waste your time talking to her personally, you know what like you know what I want about you all I did was
respond to your comments in her discord I was
Saying that I was talking shit about her and this letting her know that
You're just a, you know, kind of bitter person that is mad about something else and is trying to, uh,
Just trying to hurt my relationships and then you're saying it was a joke. It wasn't very funny. It was not funny at all. Actually, it was actually
That was a snake move. That was a little bad
Yeah
Do you try to come up here?
I had heard he came up here the other night trying to say, oh, I got some news on j-dog about you on jimmies or something like that
Um, no, what he has said he was trying to get he's over there trying to spread lies again
Well, I had got into it with Tommy James. I mean him arguing and I told him okay
Well show me your body you want to rip off your shirt show me your body
Let's rip off our shirts like rip off her shirt and then he didn't get up ripping off his shirt
And he says oh J dog. You're gay. I'm gonna go tell psyche about this. That's what he's talking about
Yeah, so that's like
KZ that's not enough story for me to like
Sorry, I'm gonna bring you on because I know I know you're like
No, I've had you on panel before it sounds like this
And then it's like you'll say like five, you know five words the whole time and it's like I mean
So I just know what kind of gets your so I mean
It's like if you'd like if you'd like some airtime
KZ on my show so bad because you've been coming here almost every day begging to come on the air
Yeah, you don't want to like you know
Donate one dollar so why am I gonna waste my time? Why am I gonna waste my time?
I shouldn't even like you know what be an idea if he if he really is that broke and he really get you know
Don't have all the you know the full amount every day. He comes
Why don't he donate a dollar and then at the end of 25 days then he could come up?
You know, that's a donation goal right there every day donate $1 and then at the end of that
Yeah, little like, you know jar like a jar and count
Yeah, yeah, the complaining wasting mine and everybody's time
I'm just wanting like a little, you know, codler in the chat every day, right?
Why don't you like, you know, just, you know, throw a couple coins my way.
Maybe I'll be like a little more sensitive to hearing your side, your side, you know, speak the side,
but you're welcome to talk in the chat all you want.
I'm not really going to pay attention.
I'm not going to like the, I refuse to be extorted to the tarot community.
Well.
Okay, Jay um KZ, you know if you think it's extortion, you know, I really don't want you to like, you know feel that way
So why are you here first of all and why don't you just disappear?
And I'll I can actually hate to make make that happen
Everybody join hands in a circle around KZ and we're gonna do a cold sacrifice
Okay
Okay, let's see no
Uh
I don't have to hear him at all and oh my gosh, that's it's even better than the 25 dollars. I don't have to look look at his comment
Dude, he then he complains why this happens to him look what he does look at his actions
He's a very annoying person.
I've never encountered anything like, you know,
with such a ridiculous personality, but...
Hey, Kasey, how about, yeah, go to your own show,
where all the only thing that's on his show
is clips of my show, and so I don't know
if we're going to use on his show.
Dude, is he another AMC?
Is he possibly...
He would like just re-stream when he was on my panel
like a few times, and so that's all I see
on his channel, like I don't...
Oh, okay.
But anyway, you know, if you go and then you're accusing me of like extortion and whatever to the terror, the terror community. No, basically, you know, you know, in front of like a lot of people, and, you know, in an untrue way. And so you are, you know, you had a fine, you don't want to pay the fine. You don't have to. You don't have to be on my panel either. You can make a decision about it. I can make a decision about it. Okay.
Yeah, it's called the troll toll like time said, right?
Yeah
He doesn't want to play the troll toll and can't cross the bridge. It's like I can understand man
Right and it's like and that's the only person, you know, I'm trying to charge to go on panel
Sometimes I will occasionally like have a sponsored panel. It's not like I'm trying to it's not like I'm asking people are saying
Oh, he charges everybody. Have I charged anybody any of you to come on panel? No
I've uh
had a sponsored panel where I, you know, put, you know, whatever you want on the banner on the banner and it opened the panels to anybody and let you kind of, you know, maybe even run the panel, or, you know, have some like a lot of incident stuff on the panel.
So that's like a, just a way I tried monetizing. What is it? I mean, it's like people have such fault with everything I do, everything. I can't even like.
like, um, like Ambeda's when she said, like, oh, um, you know, there's the HIV
Awakens Tarot Ambeda's chat.
And then, oh, I just turned on the, um, her show at one time and I heard her
saying, oh, HIV Awakens, you know, you know, change your name.
And then Eldo was like, no, no, no, no, no, don't have him change his name.
You know, that's good.
You know, it's fine.
And she's like, no, I don't want that up there.
And then it's turned into like, now I was saying that Eldo is HIV Awakens Tarot.
No, I just, but I did say.
You know, thank you be it for being fair about that. I didn't say anything else besides that
But now it's turned into like I was accusing M. L. Doe being that and now Christine thinks I'm
HIV awakens tarot like like I would make that kind of name up and like have myself
Oh with what part what are you talking about? I can't just agree with something. Oh hell yeah, I agree 100% with psyche
Oh, okay. I thought you were talking about I didn't know what you were talking about. That's why I wanted to get clarification
Yeah, Jada somewhat the stuff that psyche was bringing up like the stuff he was just talking about now. Oh, yeah, yeah 100%
It's like if you have you do people agree or disagree. It's fine
But there's ways of like expressing agreement or disagreement. And so that's also like a thing
it's like a lot of people just want to disagree with me by by a
Responding with slander and lies and things like that people keep people can say it's my vape making the kissing noise. No, it's not like it
No, not my vape
I don't know where that sound was coming from though. I never really heard it. It's okay. It's a problem. It might be the bait because it is like, you know, there's like, you know, here, here. Well, it wasn't again. Let's try again, Helen.
I didn't know either I didn't know I didn't know I didn't know what it was either but if it was the vape my back
It's okay.
I never smelt I never smelt sage before. So go to like a you know whole foods or something
They have these little bundles of like and it's like a
kind of bark or part of a plant you burn it and it's like that's really good. It's good for
cleansing the environment and stuff. So it smells really good. I like to play with incense. I like this
You think guys you like so I can't hurt it sound so I can hurt it sound just now that you're talking
Yeah, it's the it's the car right now. Hold on
It's okay. It's fine
Yeah, thank you guys for hitting the like yeah, and it's like unfortunately like you know, I just have people like trying to
Yeah, if everyone can hit the like because I do have like a lot of trolls that are just trying to like, you know, not like
And so, you know, go ahead and show some support for the chat. So you two doesn't think I'm like so
such a
usual whatever so
How's everyone doing?
Hi guys. Halo. Thank you for thinking for that. Hey Nancy money for 20 by I miss anybody. I'm sorry time also
So like did you ban anybody today or no? No, I'm not banning one person in chat. Nope
Okay, I would only I only usually ban if it's like the certain person who I know it is and uncertain all that
I know it is and it's just like, you know, just ropes in the wrong way and he keeps coming on
It's basically one person guys. You can check out my community wall too because I did receive a gift of the two bags of gardeners
premium
That was today
Um, it was it came out yesterday. Actually, it was, you know, Oh, okay. Okay. I thought he did it again. I was like, what's that?
Yeah, yeah, it came yesterday. But I mean I had like 10 bags and a few weeks ago, but you know, somebody somebody took those away
So I've got I have a I got some more of it and it's like wow
I'm so excited to put that into my garden. It's actually like, you know, really a good quality
fertilizer basically, you know filtered
you know, premium cow manure without any, you know, weeds or grass, and there's just a...
I'm so excited. Thank you so much for the gift. I really appreciate it, but...
for the whoever's sending those unpaid pizzas or sending the know that someone was looking for a long over that they
Yeah, yeah
People that worked at the guitar center yesterday. They remembered me. I used to be somebody who used to go there on a regular
How did you forget you Mason? I would never if you if you walk into my store
Certainly remember you they were like, oh my gosh, you know like lost so psyche psyche
They were happy to see me after all the time
Maybe you should get a job. Oh, you know what psyche?
You know what Mason? Where do you live at? You live it? I mean not not not I'm not trying to dox like like what area is it kind of like
Like I live in New Orleans. I'm in the New Orleans area
That's a lot of it. Hey psyche psyche wasn't there a number that you had and you were wondering like why it was coming from that?
Well, there's a new world
Also, they can have fake, you know, they can get on. No, no, I'm just saying I get that just click in my head right now
I was like, what if it was what a Mason was trying to call you like like, you know for something by accident
I don't know, but I do have a I do have a sound board with the biscuit
Taste the biscuit
That was a request from the chat
I'm like an added actually a lecture sent me another
Biscuit sound I can maybe look for a moment
Yeah, she sent me another
Really cool sound clip. I think it was like a cat and a tree and I haven't heard it yet
But I think it is another another you like biscuits Mason. What do you think about biscuits? Oh?
Biscuits are good. Oh, yeah, I miss you
You like a Mason or no
Thank you. What wait? What do you say? I can't say you got biscuits
Yeah, I like biscuits man, but psyche is true though the people at the guitar center
They're like hey, I remember you man. He's the company different
You know what you are
You know if anybody has anything else, you know things anything else
You're wrong because he's an awesome. Wait, wait, psyche. Why'd you ask me if I like biscuit stuff? I just wondered
Because you know biscuits are the new craze apparently. There's this meme about biscuits that is
Beta has made it gain popularity again, you know, and so I just was wondering if you may sense
Yeah, Mason you ever had biscuits on a Persian plate
Those are the best things ever a Persian style plate with some biscuits some fresh biscuits and some mustard on top of it
I never had a biscuit sandwiches from like McDonald's or something like that, but they have that next time you do
Ronald or KFC maybe
I got it from McDonald's psyche when they have biscuits there, biscuits sandwiches
You ever have the McRiddle which it has like you know like pancakes as the bread, you ever heard that?
No
Mason I think Mason I think we've lost Mason. Oh, oh Mason. Are you there?
Okay, no, yeah, let me see if I can get the new bit
Okay, okay here look guys
Anyone who's been requesting this? Oh, I have to delete something. Let me see. I can delete this thing right here, okay?
I'll delete that and I'll add this okay, and I hope you guys enjoy this
Thank You Electra for the
Cute biscuit clips, okay one
Taste the biscuit one here there goes the crack it oh
There goes the crack it
I don't, I guess that wasn't a Biscuits song, but I still liked it.
I was like, oh, here's Mason's back.
Hi.
Saki, you asked me about Biscuits.
Remember you asked me about Biscuits?
Because there's a new craze.
Have you heard about the, um, there's this wonderful band?
You know, I think it's Bea Arthur and her husband are singing in a mall about the honey sauce and biscuits and stuff. It's really hilarious.
Hey, Alex.
No, Psyche. No, Psyche, I had biscuits from McDonald's before, man, but that was like about it, I think.
I mean, it's like, everyone's into the biscuits now, right? So...
I did make an AI song, but it's like...
No, I think I went too far with that didn't I?
It was supposed to be like a cute little good nature thing
but it didn't turn into like a
People thought it was klanders, so I'm just not mom give my other orders outside
You talking to your mom's there? Yeah, okay. I thought you were calling mom. Thank you. I'm sorry
Like it. Hold on. Thank you. I didn't I should have
Muted for that psyche. I didn't mean to do that. Okay. No problem. No problem. I didn't know your mom was always watching
Hey, Mrs. Uh, maybe I miss is nice. Oh, I'm sorry. That's okay. My bad. I
Didn't mean to interrupt you man. My bad. I'm sorry
I I have a big mouth. So, please do. Um, yeah, psyche. I was supposed to psyche. I was supposed to click me when I did that though. I didn't mean to do that out loud.
Next time. Next time. Well, we live in my life. Yeah. Yeah. No worries, guys. Hi, Alexandra. How are you?
There we go. So, anyway, Mason, uh, I'm happy that you played the drums in the mall. I'm happy. I'm going to try to get that clip, you know, and so everyone can.
So, I guess you recorded me. So, I guess you recorded me when I was on the drums.
Your mom?
My mom, yeah.
I guess. I'm fucking good.
She did. Yeah. She recorded me.
My second guess would have been
the guitar center cashier.
I would be like, but I got it.
No, but no, but the guy for
no, but the guy from the guy
from the guitar center, he
watched me though play on the
drums to the one that knows
me there and stuff like that.
I was so close to it. Yeah.
Yeah. No, no, but psyche was
really my mom that recorded it
though. I believe you. I believe
and hey mrs mason you're doing a great job with this guy i said to your mom what did you say i
said she did a good she did a good job raising you because you're a you're a good nature yeah yeah
yep so how's everyone doing like what time is it in los angeles it is now
almost about six p.m can you get some headphones from oh who is who you're asking brice
Um, so I can't it's like I still visit my mom time to time though. I still get to see her time to time
Okay, she's over but she's over there right now
Yeah, I'm visiting with her psyche, but I live like you know, right normally live
Why are you why are you hanging out with me when your mom's there?
Because I'm just on here for a little while. So I got that I already spent time with her earlier
So I guess I'm a mom earlier. Okay. Just make sure you do hang out with her
You know, it's like I think you know, I'm sure she wants to yeah and time with you when you're over there. So
Did you have dinner? Yeah?
I'm about to yeah, I can make me guess. Are you having biscuits for dinner?
No, thank you. I'm getting Chinese food for my mom and I both that's what I ordered. Okay
They have biscuits in China. I'm just wondering. I don't know if they have biscuits in China. No, I don't think they do
You know what they call cookies in England Mason
They're fortune cookies, right? That's what they call them in China. That's in China, but you know in England, you know what they call
cookie
No, they call them biscuits
That's what they call them
I like I like one good wonton soup a good sweet and sour wonton soup. Mm-hmm. Do you like egg drop soup psyche?
I do. I love Chinese food. I just haven't had in a long time, but I do love Chinese food
Please one of my favorite Chinese food is they have these like duck chicken
No, it's duck in like a little like with other like a really good sauce on it and like this little it's like a taco
but it's the more of like a like kind of like a pastry or like a
Reddit like I don't know but a doughy kind of shell. It's really good
Does it come in those packets psyche like the sauce talking about no, I'm from a restaurant from a restaurant
I used to yeah, but the
Yeah, but you put them on top of it, right like you open it up in the packets and then put it on it
Yeah, I think probably, you know, you, oh shit, you can probably like, you know, they probably have some Chinese dishes.
I also went to this place called like a dumpling restaurant with my
idea of this woman. She was like the Empress of Dumplings in downtown LA. It was pretty damn good.
When was the last time you had Chinese food? It's like quite a while because the only Chinese restaurant around here is a Panda Express, and that's not my favorite, but you don't like Panda Express that good?
it's okay kind of like Chinese fast food you know what actually the food most of the Chinese food
in America though I've been to China right and it's like the food the Chinese food in America
I enjoy more than the Chinese food I eat in China not kind of ironic but like a good egg roll oh
also my sister-in-law is Chinese she's a Chinese national that uh and she always brings like these
really interesting Chinese pitches to like you know family events and so I get to so that's
I like it. I love a good egg roll. Oh damn. Yeah, look at the cabbage and the psyche. Like you like the egg rolls
Is there egg and egg rolls though? I'm not sure is there? I don't know
Yeah, the cream of some young guy, that's a delicious soup. Have you ever had that Mason the cream of some young guy soup?
You can never mind never mind, okay
There's a joke win. Oh psyche. No psyche. I was busy. No psyche. I was doing something
It's okay. Okay, and it says uh easy saying
Okay, sharon de raton. What is that? What is chicharon de raton?
You know what that is mason
I don't know what it is, chicharón de ratón?
What is that?
Why is there little icons of rat?
It has to do with a rat.
It has to get the skin of a rat.
Oh!
Yeah.
There's even a chicken in that.
He put a chicken in his mouth.
I know you too.
Ling Ling Ling?
Yeah.
Do you know Chinese Maison?
Do you speak Chinese?
I think we lost Mason again.
Mason?
Uh-oh.
OK.
Well, anyway.
Hey, where's Ghost?
Ghost, are you there?
You've been on mute for about half an hour.
I think he fell asleep.
Ghost, if you fell asleep, come back when you wake up,
my friend, OK?
I want to do this kind of thing right here, where, look.
We can all be on next to each other,
and I can be the middle.
There we go.
Love it.
Maybe a sandwich right there psyche. I'm you know what this is called Mason is called a psyche sandwich, and you know what you and J dog are the
sandwich bread
Mason Mason come back when you're done with your dinner. Okay. Love you. I'll talk to you later
Yeah, I don't know dude Mason. I think he was had bad internet connection or something
Mason and Mason is a good guy and
Okay, anyone want to come up with me in my link and
No, I have my dinner tonight. I guess I'm not even for dinner
Basically, I had every day
Double cheeseburger, I used to drive on the way home, I basically just stuff them in my mouth and then I have to put the coffees
I might of course put my Irish cream into it if I'm feeling a little bit daring
Oh, it's wrong, babe
Oh, baby
Uh oh, kitty
He's looking for super scrap metal people like where are they right? We have people knocking all the time
Nobody came today psyche a little bit pretty pretty quiet today
No, just you know, but you know just yesterday last night they dropped up those bags of fertilizer
I just you know, I just haven't carried it in the backyard yet. So
From my door, but you just put a sign out there man
Make like a little sign just put put it out there and just like hey even hang it on the doorknob and just be like
Oh
Yeah, but I'm but I needed the fertilizer and also I throw the fertilizer into the fire here make really cool color
Okay
I didn't know about that
Yeah, well, I'm gonna try it because now I can't now I have plenty to experiment with but it's like
Doesn't even like the thing about this this is a fertilizer. It doesn't even smell. It doesn't like it's just like, you know
Really like nice
It's a good brand of it because it's like, you know pretty much odorless
I really do appreciate the gift, whoever sent me those two bags of fertilizer last time.
Bro, would they need to just send the fucking pizza paid for or not?
Bro, like if they send the pizza paid for, that'd be cool, right?
Like, that'd be nice.
It would be, but I mean, it's like, you know, I'm not holding my breath for a paid pizza.
But I do hope that the person gets to keep the pizza though.
You want to see Psyche say this in the most particular state of the day,
I don't say that much that it's like too like, you know...
I try to state facts mostly right so it's like I don't know yeah you're not really saying anything
like I like to psyche like seriously like like straight up like man to man do you feel like
kiss your ass or anything like that like if there's times like you feel like if I do that like
you can like tell me like bro okay like too little too much or yeah yeah I really don't think
you're yes man like it's like yeah not like being like too like argument or like we're not arguing
about anything so it's like what's he gonna say
no i don't like biscuits or something i don't know i don't know no but i could
bet that most of the shit you're saying like a hundred percent i would say and i would agree
with just even if i wouldn't even know you or nothing like that so it's like i agree with you
a hundred percent i have nothing to do with oh i'm you know i'm a yes man or anything like that
yeah and you know i i would agree he's very he's very observant right and uh
You know what a gum shoe is
I've heard of the term before but I'm I don't know what the criminology is for like a PI basically
Oh, okay, okay
All the electric cords cut them off and like the motors out of them can be the part that
there's copper and a lot of copper actually they'll can be copper.
Yeah I mean but it's like yeah actually I do have them next time someone comes I have a
my old monitor doesn't work anymore so I can just like give them that I want to give people like
I hate when people leave here disappointed.
It's just like, I think it's bad juju.
I want people to leave my house happy,
but I didn't have a long road for the old Japanese man
that came yesterday, but everyone was really nice though.
Actually, they're scrapper army.
It's like, they're pretty nice people
and I had no problem with anybody that's come over.
Sometimes they knock really loud,
but I think they've been told, like,
Grandpa's sleeping upstairs and just you know, and so I just right away and I try to tell them what happened and they're all
Everyone's been very nice
But now I have like because I was like how do I throw away this monitor now?
I can give it to the I can just put it out sign and I'm sure the metal person will come get it
I have a it's like I have a yeah, okay
Yeah, I have a whole like you know crew. I like basically have my own like little
Yeah, you can just put a sign out there just put free right there just stick it and say free and whoever wants it
They pick it up take it. Yeah, I'll say no bother knocking. Here's all the here's all the metal that's left
We already had there. There it is. Yep. Oh army of scrappers come for everything
Okay, so
J-Doc said that or who said that you got a jewelry box that was on legs in it sold $80. Yeah
On um on next door you can put you know free stuff sometimes or like, you know, you can like great
You got an aquarium from me maybe
Yeah
Bad Boy Breeze is pretty wild. Yeah, I don't know. I heard something about Bad Boy Breeze in reference to the Carterverse
I'd love to talk to him sometime and ask him about that if you'd like to come on the panel Bad Boy Breeze
If you don't mind I'd love to chat with you because I did see a clip on that channel with your name on it
Psychic. Can I ask you something man? Yes. Do you remember in the beginning when you first met Bita?
Did you ever know she was part of the Carterverse at all?
Like did she ever mention that to you like I think oh, I was
I just heard her mention his name and stuff, but I didn't know how
How much I think I don't know if she was involved
I'm not saying she was involved in anything like to do with anything, but the Carter verse was like, you know
What would Jim Nick said the other day I kind of disturbed me because I was like well
What about the car and Jim Nick was like well, and I was like she's like well basically
He was like just this drug addict and he was doing drugs and so
He was trolled to death basically and I was like well, that's not very good
Dude, okay
Check this out
What I'm not saying this happened
But remember how you said like okay watch it
Remember how you were saying about how you know, we're just saying like hypothetically if someone was to call like like
You know who you know who we're per you know, we're referencing
If they were to call her as a friend and be like, hey, I'm feeling well. I'm feeling like this
You know, I'm I might not be here tomorrow. I'm you know, you know, take care of stuff for me
You know, watch out. Yeah, and then they say, you know, you know, just do it. Fuck it. Just do it. Why are you calling me?
Harder
Well, that's what that's what she said about me, but she didn't say that day. She said it on her cat to everybody
Yeah, but I'm saying but I'm saying if that's her mentality
Who's to say she didn't have that same mentality towards Aaron Carter himself. I was I know what I'm saying
Yeah, and Jim Nick was like well, he was on drugs. So he deserved it basically
No, no nobody deserves to die
Nobody everybody has their own issues their own demons that they're fighting every day. Yeah, if I had somebody like that
I would like try to support them and some
Puppet master. Yeah, I think she has something to do like like with trying to you know
Pushing somebody over the edge and not caring especially if you're let's say if she let's let's just say this
I'm gonna say hypothetical. This is I'm not saying this is true. This is not even tell me for me
Psychic this is strictly me and I'll say just me my thoughts only so if anybody wants to try to be psyche
Don't go after psyche go after me. This is me saying it not psyche. These are my blocks and my beliefs only
What if?
This person was a super fan of Aaron Carter. They had a personal relationship with him, where they were so cool DMing, you know, similar to what you and her had, DMing, you know, calling, and one day she got upset with him, and he was feeling the same type of way you were at one time, and then she told him the same type of crap, you know, oh, just do it, and you know, push him over the edge.
I mean, or hypothetically, I'm talking hypothetically or about any
Yeah, he ran a celebrity. Somebody could say
Manipulate somebody that knew him or something and then make the same. I don't I don't know just hypothetically
Yeah, or even contribute in some type of way even trolling
Yeah, if these are his fan base because you know what they call his the his donators
You know what they call them? What do they call them? The disabled cuties the disabled cuties
it was like wow yeah that was that's the name of them because they called his
donators disabled cuties you know I think I don't know it's like yeah I wasn't
ignoring I was just doing stuff like well my mom for a little while that's what I
had to go do I was trying to talk to you Mason and I didn't hear anything so yeah
I don't know if you're
But, yeah, Nancy might know about that little bit about the Carterverse a little bit, I don't think that, you know, just because people are on the Carterverse, they had any bad intentions or anything like that.
Yeah, no, not everybody from that universe is bad. They're not all bad. There's good people in there too.
But the reason I was bringing it up that's why I was asking you psyche when you first met her
She never brought that up to you. Well, no, she did to you but to me
She never brought that up to me. I never knew of her
Like last year around Christmas on our show and I do remember like
Just was the most part of her thing I don't I don't know much information about it though
And I can't really find much on the internet
Then I had to be there. So I'm I'd be interested if anyone has any like more information
So I don't know, you know, who has a lot of information on the carnivorous. Yeah, I know Trisha listen
You know who Trisha literature
Yeah, she has a lot of Intel when it comes to the carnivorous, I know Trisha does have a lot of
She has a lot of knowledge when it comes to that so I don't know you know if you want to reach out to her
She might she might be able to give me some more info
I do have Trisha
I tried to talk to her today, but she was kind of in a bikini with a hat over her face sunning
But it was really cute. Oh, she was sunbathing. Oh, okay
She's in a bikini. Wow. I mean pretty band
It's just out in your yard with a, with a peak cowboy hat in a string bikini laying on the lounge chair, chatting under her hat for cute charisma.
So yeah, Nancy ends up chat chat with you about that. If you'd like to chat about it either in private or on the panel sometime, if you're, if you're willing, if you don't, if you don't want to, it's okay. I understand.
I don't want to put you in the middle of anything.
It's gonna be the holiday season. That's why I'm trying to you know, spend time with mom even though
He says the holiday season, yes, it's turning into the holiday season
Mason what are you gonna be? Halloween is coming up. Huh gonna be what's your costume? I don't know psyche yet
I'm thinking about going as you
What do you say that psyche, why would you say that I'm gonna get like that blue shirt
And drumsticks
Make sure then you could be me you just got to shave your head and you know well you got the beard already
You shave your head throwing a flannel one and you know
J-Dog
J-Dog I want to be a drummer for Christmas like this. I mean not Christmas. I meant Halloween J-Dog
Okay, okay
Who was, oh yes, I think that woman's sweet piece is that she was going to dress as me for Halloween.
What's the name? Oh, Krishalicious is her channel, Krishalicious, T-R-I-C-I-A-L-I-C-I-O-U-S is Krishalicious's channel.
And there's, um, and everybody, any mod, make sure you drop your channel too if you have a channel.
I'm also trying to put together, um, my psyche, um, psyche-verse website.
But I'm gonna put a lot of my friends on there,
like my supporters that I know,
and stuff like that on there.
Let me know if you'd really like to be on that one.
I think hopefully I can, oh, word yeah.
Hopefully I can help people out too,
and like, you know, gonna show when people are on live
and links to their channels and stuff.
So it's coming together pretty well, and I'm pretty proud.
And,
to be on that to something now, okay?
Because I'm going to try to promote in that and we're really, we're really together pretty
well.
We're pretty excited.
So, yes.
Trisha, oh yeah.
Trisha's, yeah, she was, you know, she's a, she's just a cool person, she's a really
nice person.
Who else did I talk to?
I talked to a bunch of people.
Psyche.
Yes.
Yes, Mason.
So you get to visit with your mom like anymore?
Yeah.
I do, actually, you know, my aunt passed away last year or this year, and so we're having
a little, you know, we're going to have a little get-together soon.
So, like, you work with your mom right now?
My mom is probably just home, you know.
But uh, yeah, you get to talk to her if we go to lunch and stuff, you know, I don't see her as often as I'd like but
Yeah, she's doing good
That's what's up, psyche hell yeah
So let's see what else like you love your mom and stuff like that you like to hang out with there and be with her
I love my mom.
Brando, I mean, again, you're just trolling
and it's like not funny and it's not clever or anything.
It's like, anyone can come to their own conclusion
of how I was on that show talking to Bronzeberg and Beta.
It's not a fair fight, first of all.
We're gonna say like a football team.
Yeah, a football team if they have one football player
or one team and like five football players on the other team
and then the one gets tackled,
are you gonna say, oh, he got destroyed?
I mean, maybe it's like, you know, he didn't win the football game, but was it a fair football game?
Was it, according to the rules, would it be allowed if any kind of, like, is that a huge judge?
The fairness of it based on five against one?
No, that wasn't fair at all.
That was there. That was a straight up.
How about if your microphone's not on and theirs is up all the way?
How about that, Randall? Is that fair?
You are trolling you are a troll go away or just you know come on the panel
I just a mistake of seeing your stupid comments in the chat and go away. Why are you here?
So I keep up like how are they trolling you like what do they do?
He said he's not trolling so but he's just being annoying. It's another he's just being one of those like little like
Controversy shit. Yeah, they just they're acting
Yeah
Like I was I feel like
You look at the title the video the video does not say psyche was was defeated by bronzer
It didn't say that on the title the title does something else eat the turtle like ask you the turtle if it was a fair fight, right?
Get the turtle is she like the biggest like the you know the team psyche no not necessarily, but
she was defending me and wow I was surprised but you know what I was touched and uh I'm very
appreciative thank you I you know and she you know you can whatever you want to say she was at
least impartial about it right she wanted a fair fight no one likes to see like an unfair fight right
it's like and it's like oh that's kind of like that one person was kind of like
picked on or you know right it's like
so anybody can see that i was an unfair fight right
i was like yeah probably the cowboys or i do like uh but
i'm not really that into football like i said i used to do football betting with
marty like he asked me if i could do tarot predicting games and i was like
no that's kind of a misuse of tarot but if you tell me the color of their pants
I would and then he would send me send me cash when he won and he won psyche. Yes
What was the last time it was a little when was the last time you visit your mom or spent time with your mom?
I saw my mom probably a few weeks to go for lunch. We had a little lunch. Okay. We had a nice lunch and
You know, it was all good
I'm, you know, I'm not easy to lose a parent and, you know, I've lost a parent and anybody
that has no, it's hard and the remaining parent needs, you know, love and support, right?
Yeah, but, you know, a psyche, you can always go to visit her, though, if you don't live
with her, like, wow, we don't live with our parents anymore and stuff like that.
I mean, it's very far, but I don't have a car.
And so basically I have to like whenever it's like, you know,
her schedule or when the family gets together and stuff.
I should predict the game.
Yeah.
I predicted the football.
I said, I said, I'm already called me the underdog
because I would always, I would usually say under.
And that's how I predicted the Super Bowl.
I said, I said, I said, yeah, Eagles under 50.
And then I was right.
I wish I would have bet on the Super Bowl, but fortunately, I just, uh, predicted it.
Look how gray I am. I didn't even say it was gray.
Look at it. Again, it's like, it's been my Cruella de Vil.
Look, look, half gray, half dark.
Jay Dogg!
What's up, bro?
Hey, Jay Dogg.
What's up, Mason? What's up?
Mason, he said what?
Can you hear me? I can't hear
He's saying what do you hear him at all? He's talking normally. Can you hear me?
What's that I hear I'm just fine
Okay
So, um, so, baby, Ferrari, no, I've never gotten that, I don't know.
Now, for day dogs, the only people that have sent me WangTicks are, um, the guy's Theo,
I think his name is Theo, and then, uh, Barry, but I don't know if Barry is, um, but, and
we know where he is, and he's, uh, got him through the internet.
I think it's the only, only video, just a couple of dick pics.
Damn. They're pretty nice.
So what's the plan for the night cycle you're gonna chill out man?
Actually, we're having ghost tober this weekend because you know ghosts once
fun celebration and like you know it's pretty nice things and so that morning we had Reviler Red
and Crucible Ghost. Unfortunately it's generated a little bit because Reviler Couldn't Control
You can go, actually, as soon as the movie is done.
I'll probably talk to you later.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
They have all my shows.
As long as they've got all the TV shows, as well as all the big times,
as well as all the bloggers, as well as all of you.
Who else is on there?
Sam-Mang's on there.
A lot of Channel First people are on there.
Panelverse shows are syndicated on Rumble.
You just have to look up panelverse VODs,
and you can see those deleted episodes
that maybe are too hot for a,
I think it's a J-Dog, yeah, a little bit of background noise.
You can just check that out on panelverse VODs.
I also, I think I tried to syndicate mine to Rumble,
but I don't think it worked,
and so I don't think I did it right, but.
Um, you can't hear it. Can you hear me at all? Hold on. Let me see testing one, two, three
Let me see if my right microphone is on it. I didn't have to turn on my orb one. Let me see orb
Oh, yeah, it's on. Okay. This is my orb. Can you hear me? Okay. I'm talking into it
JDoc has a background noise. It's okay. It's okay. JDoc is biting off here. Uh-oh. Come on, baby Ferrari. Don't be ridiculous
I need to learn not to read comments. Okay, so who's talking backstage? Somebody's talking backstage. It says private chat
Random guy. Okay. Yeah, it's rando from earlier. Okay. Now you can hear me. Okay. Good. I love this microphone. This is great
Better. Okay. Good
Yeah, so what do you guys think? What do you guys want to chat about right now?
What's the topic of the day? I because now it's like it seems like you know
You know Bita did ask me just to like not go to her chat or to stay away from her
and so I will be respecting her wishes and
But it might be a little bit, you know
Less drama, but I guess I'm happy to let the what was pretty funny though. What was pretty funny?
What?
But you see oh the Attila and Jules, baby. What what what J? What's funny come on? I
Don't know
What was pretty funny? I don't know. I don't know. I might
I don't know why I'm up to tonight
It's been pretty quiet today
I'm just been working on my on my website. Oh baby Ferrari with baby Ferrari said
J-Dog is spiting off his poor wife who wishes he would just come to the dinner table. Oh come on. I'm sure
She can bring a plate outside
He's sitting in the crazy things like yeah, I wasn't gonna go eat right now, too
No, I'm not leaving. No, no, no, I'm not leaving. I'm not leaving but I'm just saying no
I was gonna go eat a little while, but not right now
Okay, what do you have for dinner tonight biscuits?
No biscuits with some mustard on a nice Persian clay and then you know what I'm gonna get I'm gonna get a quesadilla
Check your quesadilla with some rice and beans. That's what we're gonna get
Yeah, I'm having I'm having a bronze a bronze fried chicken. Oh
Hell yeah, is it crispy? Is it real crispy real crispy? It's crispy
I'm serving it with betas biscuits and the honey sauce, right? Oh
Hell yeah, man. What about the sweet? What about the sweet PT?
Sweet P. T. Yeah, sweet P. T. and uh, and uh, split, split, split, split, split, split, sweet P soup and uh, who else?
And uh, I'm having a ham sandwich for dessert.
Actually, there you go. Hell yeah.
Ham sandwich.
A ham sandwich. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, hello, ham sandwich for my Bert.
Oh, she's crazy, man.
I'm gonna get in trouble for that. I'm gonna get in trouble.
I'm willing to take the heat though, okay?
Well, they can't take a joke man. We're just joking like that. It's not nobody's
The next thing I'm gonna be suit for saying ham sandwich and that's gonna be the sad day
Yeah, nobody's name was even said we were good. It was all gifts and reference nobody said nothing bad about nobody just reference
They might be a little, you know what, they have, they have, you know, they have solutions
for that, you know, they do have, you know, butter for them biscuits because, you know,
they are a little dry, especially, you know, when they sit out for that long and they're
a little stale.
Like different biscuits and like melted butter, I'm just like, oh my God, I'm a little good.
Oh, making me hungry, man, making me hungry.
I don't think he's full mass.
I'm thinking about the ham sandwich.
Well, I'm full mass, just thinking about it too.
All I want for Christmas is a hand sandwich, a hand sandwich.
It's just like a peaceful day, you know, no, I didn't get any knocks today.
Yesterday there was a knock, a guy was pissed that there was not metal left because he was apparently on the phone with somebody promising him a lot, but I think the metal community has heard about.
that they're being scammed by this guy and they're just not, they're just, why is that
Too smart
Okay, so to get to my
Like if you want to get like up to my door
You have to go through this really like a little narrow thing like a little narrow alley basically and then it's like really hard to turn
Around especially in a big truck and so they get so pissed because they spell he's been like half hour trying to get into my driveway
And a half hour. I mean, I'm just sitting here like, you know, just chillin and it's like and these people are like
Excited to get some metal and it's like there's wasting time like trying to turn away my driveway for hours
And it's like I feel worse for them that I even feel for myself
I mean, it's like I just have to like say oh, I'm so I'm sorry
No, it's prank. They have to fucking go through probably hours of you know, excitement and then the disappointment
It's just like I feel bad. I feel bad. And so
If anybody knows the metal scrapper community in redondo, you know, just spread the word, you know, I'm out of a
All I have is a TV set that they can have right
The what is the
Yes, like yeah, I gotta head out I gotta go pick up the dinner real quick and I'll be back, right man
All right, thanks Matt. I'll pick up later
So no problem you guys want to see the the delivery I got today. I'll just I'll share with you and then maybe I'll
Come back later tonight when ghost wakes up
He said he could just be for a little bit. Oh, yeah
I want to go over it actually I'll I'm gonna do a surprise for somebody because somebody did something nice for me
I'm going to do a little surprise for her, but I just want to show you this first
This is I'm gonna share the screen
This is my delivery today
Or yesterday. Let me see. It's right here. There we go. Here's my page
Okay, you see okay, I'm gonna go down a little bit my post. Okay, and there we go
Two bags of weed free and fine screened steer manure
Gardeners brand that is the top brand of manure. There's two bags of it
Yeah, it's lovely gift
Wow, what a generous donator there's also there's two you see that was sweet very nice
There's three comments, but I can only see two of them
I wonder what the third was can somebody go check with the third commenters and tell me who that was I might want to
Check out who that was. I don't know why I don't see them. They did there's not there. Let me see
and
Anyone can go look and yeah
So it's the top brand manure. It's a name brand, right? It's not that generic shit literal shit, right?
It's yeah, I'm gonna put it to good use. I have a garden in the back. It's kind of you know, my garden will be yeah
Good manure is gold, right? It's just a nice gift
But that yeah, so that's what's going on there
We'll yeah, what is wheelchair peanut butter bingo mean, what does that mean pick up the dinner? Okay? No, no come on
Um, so I think that's
Look at that. What is that? What is all this like? See those is that grass? It's supposed to be the grass that blacks with flowers on
Look at I
Mean that cow looks fucking happy
Look at this green grass
But fine screen. It's like the finest. This is a basically the good shit. It's called the good shit literally the good shit, right?
Don't lie. I bathe in manure. Why would I bathe in manure?
Does that make any sense to anybody? What is that?
The thing did I just say very nice like very nice very nice very nice. Yeah, there's no weeds
Oh, yeah, yeah, there's no reason at all go get some fucking mushroom spores and get lady
Anybody have mushroom spores?
I am looking for some so I could like, you know, trip balls.
Hey, RG, I think J-Dog's actually gayer than,
oh my gosh, come on, Black Archie.
Come on, Black Archie.
I don't think you can get too much gayer than me, but,
I mean, J-Dog's married, right?
It's gone.
It's gone, Jean.
Oh, did you say, oh yeah, very nice.
Let me see, let's see, Jamie say, let's go on, Jamie.
Okay, anyway.
Anybody, crispy chicken does some dope.
Bronze, fried chicken, and we, you know,
and Bronze Bird, he played like the,
I'll play a psyche hater, but he actually like was like,
oh, that's a good looking chicken.
And he said, it looks like a golden chicken.
I'm sorry, it is a Bronze Bird, it's a bronze chicken.
It's not gold.
Bronze kind of looks like gold, right?
But it's not, it's quite the opposite.
But we can watch that video and then we'll catch you guys
later, but okay, here we go, guys.
Enjoy. Oh, look at this thing.
That's me when I don't cut my hair.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, shit. What else do I got?
Take that down.
Yeah, I make some little, I make some cute video clips.
Let me see, video file. What else do I got?
I have...
This
Okay, anyway, oh, so here's what I was going to do guys. Let's do a friendly raid of
And I don't mean to call it a raid. Let's just like let's just go over here and be everyone be nice or whatever right?
We can go over here and hang out to give you a seizure. Well
Obviously, it wasn't that bad of a seizure if you're typing and stuff
but let's go over here to this show and just everyone say hi and psyche sent me and
It's a fun over there. Okay guys
Let me just put in the stream and I'll just play the psyche haters club on the way out. Hey everybody. I love you guys
that's uh, let's all go over to that link I just posted and
Say psyche sent you
Okay
dealio
Let's do it
Here you go
Christine's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Bronze chicken struts around, but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea is gone sour, beets has bitter betty again
Alexander had my back, that's a real one not pretend
Welcome to the site
Can pluck those feathers, toss it in the pan
Welcome to the
Taste the biscuit